It has begun! Tokimeki Balameter Ascending Formula D!
Yes, it has begun.
So, your skin is getting soooo cold.
It's autumn.
It's cool.
But it's hot at noon.
It is quite warm at noon.
I'm not sure what to wear.
A little bit and a little bit.
It's not that autumn is cold.
There are more things to do.
It's cold, cold.
I don't like cold.
I don't like it.
Like a change of clothes?
You can change your clothes.
Okay, I'll do it.
We all have more important things to do.
Autumn?
I don't know.
Eating.
Eat on your own. Reading? No, I don't.
Say muscat? No. Simultaneous game of bend and turn? I don't play.
Not doing it. A game where you add words to a ruler and answer instantly? I won't do it.
I won't do it. That's a little bit.
Everyone ran away.
We were all in shreds, weren't we? Don't you guys get it?
Hey, everybody. Everybody.Hey, guys. Hey, guys.
It's a staring contest.
Last time, I was in tatters. The staring contest.
I guess we're in a bad shape. I think the chestnut roast was a good match.
It was a mess.
What? Was I in tatters?
This time, I'm going to take revenge.
How many seconds can we stare at each other? Staring at each other 2023!
I'm back.
It's been quite a few years.
It was rather interesting, wasn't it?
The hair was sneaky, and the moment it went up was interesting.
Do you have confidence in yourself?
Yes, I do.
I'm getting stronger. Don't laugh.
You're going to laugh. If you don't laugh, I'll laugh more.
I would like to explain the rules.
The rules are based on a timed competition,
First of all, let's have everyone play rock-paper-scissors-paper,
Then, we have you decide the number of the game,
Then, we will have a lottery.
If you pick a number, you're good-looking.
If you pick a number, it's all bad.
You have to do it by lottery.
I've done it before.
We did it. With a lottery.
I've got a good sense.
I'll play any number I want.
In a tournament.Tournament.
Let's do it.
Tonki-ki-reki janken janken boy.
Number 6.
Tanami, number 2.
Number 4.
Well, let's see.
Seriously?
I don't want to do it.
Miki Kuroda?
You guys already.
Number 4.
Seed.
The seed.
A seed.
A little.
Pretend you're good at it.
Pretend you're good.
Okay, okay.
You're good.
So, which hand do you want to start with?
From the left?
Jean.
OK.
Okay.Yes.
Good luck.
Yes, sir.
Well, then, let's all do our best.
Okay, let's do our best.
Let's do it.
Oh.
This program is,
Fish and the members challenge various things,
and raise the "tokimeki barometer" of the world.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching!
Now, let's get back to the 1006th episode of Nikagurakko Daijikigoto,
This is Hitoka and Oharu.
Please tell us about the two of you.
I hope that you will look at Oharu a lot and think she is cute.
Also, I think I'm really good at drawing, so I'm going to draw with a lot of gusto.
And Oharu?
Yes, you closed your eyes last time.
That's right.
This time, I'm going to challenge to a fair competition.
Yes, a messager.
For now, I would like to follow the rules.
That's the first step.
Okay.
Is that all right?
Yes, just a moment.
Okay.
Okay? Here we go.
First round, let's get started! First round, yo, start!
Start!
Wait a minute. What do you mean?
Come on, come on, come on.
My hair.
Shabasha, kita chaan!
Here, let me get under your hair.
Your hair is bad.
It's soggy.
I've only seen this in Kyoto. It's the way they do it.
And, yeah, what's with the eyes?
I didn't look at the eyes.
By the way...
It's bad for your hair. It's bad for your hair.
Yes!
Ishida won!
Winner?
Oh, it's okay, it's okay.
Okay, then.
Last time, you played with Julia, right?
Did we?
Now, for the second round, we have Julia and Hiyorin.
Please give us your enthusiasm one by one.
Yes, I'm in the revenge round,
I'm going to show you the not-so-good game of the first round.
I feel very sorry, but I will do my best.
Sorry? For who?
For everyone.
To everyone?
Well, the way I'm feeling right now, I think I can do it.I think I can do it, the way I'm feeling right now.
Hiyo wanted to get her revenge this time, too.
That's right.
I want to make it to the finals for that reason,
I want to win here.
My hands are starting to shake a little.
So, are you two ready for this?
OK!
Okay, here we go.
The second round, let's get started!
Start!
Knock-knock-knock!
Oh, hey.
What?
I don't know what I'm looking at.
I can't talk anymore.
I'm confident I can do it.
But you did pretty well.
I see.
I noticed.
I was laughing when you pulled my hair.
What's your type right now?
My type right now is not at all.
Wider than me.
That one?
That's everyone.
Huh? This is no time to be talking about Akita.
It's bad. I fell in an instant. Oh no. I fell in an instant.
It's not good.
Oh, no.
Okay, bye.
Nice to meet you.
I'll be waiting for you myself.
How's it doing?
It's cracking already.
Last time it was so bad that I would blow up when I got mad, but this time I've got it under control.
I've grown up a little bit.
It's growing, seriously.
But the vibrations are making me nervous.
Can you feel it?
It's throbbing.
I'm telling you, I'm nervous.
We can all win.
Let's do the finals, shall we?
Okay, so that's the third round.
These two will be in the final if one of them wins.
That's too close.
Then, what is your enthusiasm for each of them?
I feel like I can make it.
I really do.
I feel like I can do it.
That's good.
Just like before the first round.
I saw it, I saw it a while ago.
Really?
I saw it just a few seconds ago.
Sorry, Aki-chan. I'm sorry, I'll go first.Sorry, Aki-chan. Go ahead.
Sorry.
Oh no, I'm going to lose.
My heart is absolutely racing.
My heart is racing.
I'm nervous.
It's going faster.
I don't know what to do.
Oh no.
But if I win here, I will do my best to show my usual gap.
So I'll see you later.
Let's go.
All right, let's go.
First of all?
Iqué.
Good night.
Hey, you know what?
The corners of your mouth keep twitching.
Red only?
I couldn't see.
I just wanted to look at her all the time, like she's so cute and adorable.
But Julia's...
It's like I've been to Kyoto too.
It's so bad. It's like the capital of Japan.
I feel like I'm in Kyoto.
Yo, Don!
That was a good fight.
That was a little long.Now that was a little long.
What's the time?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
7.4.
Next.
Aki-chan, you're up next.
One word, Julia.
Wow, that's nice.
I'm in the statue of the feeling that I never laugh.
I'm in a state of mind not to laugh, so I'm going to prove it for the third time.
I lost here last time, so I'd like to win this time.
So, can you see me? No, no, no.
Julia looks like she can handle it. My heart's starting to race.
Here we go. All right, let's go.
I laughed.
Yay!
Thank you.
The audience was important, too.
And I'm laughing all the way through.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm going to the flower garden.
I shouldn't have been there, but I lost.
Same fight again?
Same again.
It's like this, after all.
I knew it!
Exactly the same!
And now for the finals.
The finalists are Julia and Aki-chan!
What's your enthusiasm?What is your enthusiasm?
Yes, I am.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
I already washed the dance.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm the winner of the last one.
The secret to winning last time was... turn your face around.
You know, like a little arrow tongue in the face or something.
But you didn't do that today.
I want to show the five of you that you don't have to do that.
I'd like to show the five of you that you can win without doing that.
Oh, that's great.
I lost in the finals last time.
I'll do my best to be the champion this time.
I'm going to win.
Don't you see what's happening?
Yes, I can.
Okay, let's go.
Let the finals begin!
Oh!
Ooh...
Ooh.
oh?
Oh.
Hey, what's this?
Akichan's.
Correct!
I got it! I got it!
I don't know.
It's just his voice.
His voice...
The voice.
Oh, that's smart.
What's more, you know...
I gave you a wide angle at first.
I don't see any mistake at all.
I gave you a wide angle.
You said no.
I'm sorry.
So, let's see...
Who's the champion?
Anshan!
Yes!
It's open!
That's great.
I think we're about to hear an important battle.
Important! The big, big, big fight.
What's the point?
What's the bottom line?
You saw my glasses, right?
Oharu, Hiyori, Kagami.
Even the lowest C? The lowest C?
Don't you want the lowest C?
Weren't these the same three last year?
That's right.Yes, yes, yes.
Somehow the same, exactly the same.
Rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors!
Hey!
Oharu got a C
Oh, we're already there.
C
Let's move back. The loser gets to play Kotakazuka.
That's right, that's right.
Okay, let's go.
Okay.
What? The bottom C?
Oh, my God!
I can't do this anymore.
I can't do this anymore, Hiyori.
You really didn't say that.
Aki-chan, you want to do it? You're so cute.
I can't do it anymore
I'll be fourth.
All right.
Don't talk about autumn being cold.
Come on.
I can't anymore.
Okay, let's start with you, Ms. Kanami.
What's your enthusiasm for the race to the bottom?
Yes, I am.
Hiyori-n's been working hard today.
I think she can win.
Next, Hiyori, please.Then, Hiyori, please continue.
I missed the pressure point.
Why?
I can't.
Just a minute.
You can't.
What?
What pressure points?
Not that many.
Oh, God.
What?
What? Today.
Oh...
Hiyori, put some C in there.
Hey, stop it.
Hiyori.
You shouldn't laugh.
No, no, no, Chiku-san, I want you to bully me.
You're standing on the side of the stage.
That's right.
You have to control your emotions and play with them.
It's appropriate to be on the side of the stage.
Zone on the back
One hit.
A little harder.
Yeah. - Okay.
There you go.
It's not in there. Is it okay?
It was pretty hard. It'll be fine.
I feel like a broken doll.I feel like a broken doll.
Oh, my God, I did it. Is everything okay?
Excuse me, excuse me, excuse me. You had a side-eye?
Both of you?
Hey...
Yes, please.
Ready?
Boom!
Ha-ha-ha!
What is this?
What's this?
It's going on, it's going on.
I want to show you one more time.
All right.
Are you done?
What? This is Kanami, right?
You're hurting me.
Well, Kanami's the winner.
That's great.
Hiyori and I are up against each other.
Isn't Kanami's face so funny?
I wish I could've seen it.
This is the last game of the season, so please tell us about your enthusiasm for the last game.
Well, I'm going to do my best to get ready for the final match.
Hiyori, go ahead.
I won't lose!
What's this?
I don't want to be in last place.
Because I brought this project to you.I brought this project to you.
I can't lose.
You've made me realize it.
Then, since you said you're ready...
I'll get started.
Here we go.
Dong!
Ah!
Winner.
Good morning.
Me? You have to know this place.
I'm feeling it!
I will now announce the winner.
The 2nd, Don't Laugh! The second annual "Don't Laugh!
Who will be the winner?
The memorable bottom runner?
Yes, Hiyori Yoshikawa. Congratulations!
The lowest ranked and the highest ranked will unexpectedly win, right?
That's true.
Surprisingly.
It's all right.
I can do it.
I've given up.
I gave up.
I'm sorry. I'm stressed.
I can do it.
I can do it. I can go.
They won't split it with me.
Now, we have a special game.
Let's get to it.
Let's go!
Hmm?
Ah.
Thank you very much.
You make a funny sound.
What's this?
Ha-ha-ha.
My neck's on fire.
Neck.
What's the odds of that?
Strong.
Gentlemen! Gentlemen! Gentlemen!
Hey!
Yeah!
Sounds like a neck.
Isn't this awesome?
Is that Nilaa Neko?
What is this a showdown?
What's the showdown?
Oh, my God.
What is it?
Akichan's white
Is it a highlight?
Is it a highlight?Maybe it's a highlight.
Uh, maybe.
Oh, great.
That's great.
That was magnificent.
So, ladies and gentlemen...
How was it?
The 2nd Niraneko Tournament
Wow!
It was surprisingly difficult!
I was so happy!
But I've got to get myself ready for this thing on the side.
I have to manage my facial expressions.
I think it's very important to make adjustments.
So let's all work on that.
Let's work on that.
Okay, so thank you very much for watching.
Thank you very much.
Let's cut the second level waist.
If you laugh, you lose.
Oh, how's that?
Bye-bye.
Goodbye, goodbye. Thank you for yesterday.
After the rain, the streets are turning colors.
And on the canvas of my broken heart, I'll paint a piece of the future.
And lead us to the future.
Thank you for watching.Thank you for watching!
Now I can tell you why I cried.
Whenever you're lost, just remember
So that you can laugh even when it rains
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny sky, making puddles of sound
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny day, let my tears dry
I'm gonna wear a rainbow dress
Lalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalala
Please subscribe to our channel!
undefined